About Fluid Truck

Our services

Our services

Our Vehicles

©2024 Fluid Market Inc.

Privacy Policy
==============

This Privacy Policy was last updated on January 15, 2021  
  
Fluid Market Inc.("Fluid") understands your concerns about how your information is collected, used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This Privacy Policy lets you know what information we collect when you use the Fluid application and website, www.fluidmarket.com("Services"), and how we use such information, with whom we share it, how we protect it, and the choices we offer you regarding our collection and use of such information. By accessing and using the Services, you acknowledge your consent to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Services.  
  
Your use of the Services is also governed by our Terms & Conditions found at https://www.fluidtruck.com/terms-and-conditions.

#### 1\. Types of Information We Collect

When you use the Services, we collect information that identifies, relates to, describes, is reasonably capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly with a particular individual or household (“personal information”), as well as information that cannot on its own uniquely identify you. We collect this information in several ways:  
  
**Information you voluntarily give us**  
Registration information. If you sign up for an account or use the Services, we may collect certain personal information from you, such as your name, address, telephone number, mobile phone type and carrier information and email address, credit card information, motor vehicle records, insurance information, email address, etc. Upon registration, we may also collect information about you that does not uniquely identify you, such as information related to your account settings and preferences, if you choose to provide us with such information.  
  
**Information from other sources**  
Usage and Device Information. When you access and use the Services, we may collect certain information by automated means, such as cookies and web beacons. A "cookie" is a text file that websites send to a visitor's computer or other Internet-connected device to uniquely identify the visitor's browser or to store information or settings in the browser. A "web beacon," also known as an Internet tag, pixel tag or clear GIF, is used to transmit information back to a web server. We also may use third-party website analytics tools (including Google Analytics) that collect information about visitor traffic on the Services. The information we may collect by automated means may include (i) usage information such as your IP address, browser information and other information related to your visit to and use of the Services; and (ii) information about the device you use to access and use the Services, such as your hardware model, operating system version, unique device identifiers and mobile network information including your phone number. All usage and device information may be associated with your Fluid account.  
‍  
Location Information. When you access and use the Services using a mobile device, we may collect and process information about your actual location through GPS signals or other technologies that determine location, including, but not limited to device latitude/longitude, accuracy, heading, speed, and altitude, cell tower and Wi-Fi access point information. All location information may be associated with your Fluid account. If you consent to providing Fluid, or our third party partners, with your location information, we monitor, collect and use your wireless location information, as well as other information obtained from our platform and your device, to provide you with Services. This information may include, but is not limited to: GPS data (including, but not limited to device latitude/longitude, accuracy, heading, speed, and altitude), cell tower and Wi-Fi access point information. You can use your wireless device to obtain a wide array of services based on the approximate location of the device, referred to as Location-Based Services, or LBS. you participate in an LBS campaign, you will receive prior notice and must give your consent before your location is used or shared.  

#### 2\. How We Use Your Information

We use the information we obtain about you to (i) register you for an Fluid account; (ii) provide services you have requested; (iii) provide you with location-based services ("LBS") when you participate in an LBS campaign; (iv) provide you and Borrowers or Sharers (as defined in the Fluid Terms and Conditions) with information related to you and your share or items; (v) respond to your questions and comments and provide customer support; (vi) operate, evaluate and improve the Services and our business; (vii) analyze trends and statistics regarding visitors' use of the Services; and (vii) enforce our Terms and Conditions or other agreements.  
‍  
We may also utilize information obtained from you to collect additional information about you from our third-party partners and may combine information that we obtain from you with information from such third-party partners. Examples could include motor vehicle record search data, credit reporting agencies, insurance reporting providers, etc.  
‍  
We may also use the information we obtain about you in other ways with your consent.  

#### 3\. How We Share Your Information

We may sell, rent or disclose non-personal information we collect without restriction. Fluid does not sell, rent or disclose to third parties any of your personal information except in the limited circumstances described in this Privacy Policy.  
  
We may disclose your personal information as necessary to (i) comply with a law, regulation or legal request; (ii) enforce or apply our Terms and Conditions or other agreements; or (iii) protect the rights, property, or safety of Fluid and any person. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.  
  
We may engage our third-party partners, service providers, or individuals to perform functions on our behalf and will provide them with personal information and other information as necessary for them to perform their functions. For example, we may engage third parties to conduct data analysis, process payments, and provide customer service.  
  
In the event that Fluid is involved in a bankruptcy, merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets, information about you may be sold or transferred as part of that transaction. We will use reasonable efforts to direct any transferee to use your information in a manner consistent with this Privacy Policy.  

#### 4\. Your Choices

We offer you the following choices about what information we collect from you and how we communicate with you:  
  
Cookies. Most browsers will tell you how to stop accepting new cookies, how to be notified when you receive a new cookie, and how to disable existing cookies. Please note, however, that without cookies you may not be able to take full advantage of all of the features of the Services. We may also use cookies for marketing and targeted advertising purposes.  
  
Marketing Emails and Texts. You may choose not to receive marketing emails and text communications from us by clicking on the unsubscribe link in the marketing emails or by texting the word STOP to the short code from which you are receiving Fluid text messages.  
  
Location Information. When you use access and use the Services on your mobile device, you may choose not to share your location details with us by adjusting your device's location services settings. For instructions on changing the relevant settings please contact your service provider or device manufacturer.  

#### 5\. Security

Fluid uses reasonable security efforts to protect your personal information. Please note, however, that no electronic transmission of information can be entirely secure. We cannot guarantee that the security measures we have in place to safeguard personal information will never be defeated or fail, or that those measures will always be sufficient or effective.  

#### 6\. Policy Towards Children

Our Services are not directed to persons under 13. Fluid does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from, anyone under the age of 13. Any personal information we receive from people we believe to be under 13 will be deleted from our system. If you become aware that your child has provided us with personal information without your consent, please contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.fluidtruck.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) and we will delete such information from our system.  

#### 7\. Access and Correction

You may obtain a summary of your personal information retained by us, or modify, correct, change or update such information by contacting Fluid as provided below. You can also request to have Fluid remove personal information you have previously provided to us by contacting us using the contact information provided below. In some cases, removal may be impossible. Right to Delete: All users have the right to request the deletion of personal information, subject to certain limitations.  
  
**California Privacy Rights**  
The California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”) gives California residents certain rights in relation to their personal information and requires the provision by us of some additional information. Any terms defined in the CCPA have the same meanings when used in this section. This notice is intended to supplement the information provided elsewhere in this Privacy Policy with information specific to California residents.  
  
In the past 12 months, we have collected the following categories of personal information:  
\- Identifiers, such as name, postal address, IP address, and email address.  
\- Personal information categories listed in the California Customer Records statute (Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.80(e)), such as a name, postal address, telephone number, motor vehicle records, or payment information.  
\- Commercial information, such as a record of products or services purchased, obtained, considered, or other purchasing or consuming histories.  
\- Internet or other similar network activity, such as browsing history, search history, information on a consumer’s interaction with a website, application, or advertisement.  
\- Geolocation data, such as physical location or movements.  
\- Inferences drawn from other personal information, such as a profile reflecting a person’s preferences, characteristics, psychological trends, predispositions, behavior, attitudes, intelligence, abilities, and aptitudes.  
  
The CCPA provides the following rights:  
_Right to Know:_ California residents have the right to request information about the categories and specific pieces of personal information we have collected, as well as the categories of sources from which such information is collected, the purpose for collecting such information, and the categories of third parties with whom we share such information. California residents also have the right to request information about our sale or disclosure for business purposes of personal information to third parties.  
  
Right to Delete: California residents have the right to request the deletion of personal information, subject to certain limitations.  
  
Right to Opt-Out of the Sale of Personal Information: California residents have the right to opt out of the sale, as that term is defined in the CCPA, of personal information to third parties. We do not sell personal information to third parties. We do not sell the personal information of minors under 16 years of age without affirmative authorization.  
  
Right to Nondiscrimination: California residents have the right to not be discriminated against for exercising any of these rights.  
  
If you would like to exercise one or more of the above rights, you can contact us by email at [\[email protected\]](https://www.fluidtruck.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or mail using the postal address provided below. We may need you to provide additional information to verify your request, such as providing data elements so that we can confirm they match the information already maintained by us. We will not use this additional information for anything other than handling your request. Please note that you may designate an authorized agent to make a request under the CCPA on your behalf.  
  
Additionally, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits visitors to the Services who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. We do not share personal information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes.  

#### 8\. Links and Third Party Websites

Our Services may contain links to other websites for your convenience and information. These websites may be operated by companies not affiliated with Fluid. Fluid is not responsible for links to or content of any websites not affiliated with Fluid, any use of those websites, or the privacy practices of those websites. We recommend that you review the content and policies of all websites that you visit.  

#### 9\. Modifications and Updates to this Policy

Fluid reserves the right to update or modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If we make a material change to our Privacy Policy, we will indicate via email or notice on Fluidmarket.com that our privacy practices have changed and provide a link to the new policy. The date this Privacy Policy was last revised is identified at the top of this page. Please review www.fluidmarket.com/Privacy Policy to check for any updates or changes.  

#### 10\. Contact Us

You can contact us at:  
  
Fluid Market Inc.  
PO BOX 351618  
Westminster, CO 80035  
  
Or by Email: [\[email protected\]](https://www.fluidtruck.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)  

Fluid Truck

Explore

Top cities

Connect

©2024 Fluid Market Inc.

Fluid Truck

Explore

Top Cities

Connect

©2021 Fluid Truck, Inc.

First and last name

Email addressCompanyCity

Phone numberCompany typeSelect one...FleetLeasingRentalOtherState

Business fleet size (owned vehicles)Select one...25-99100-499500+How many total vehicles would you like to list on our platform?

Please submit ONLY if you are interested in listing 25+ vehicles.

By submitting this form you are opting-in to receiving Fluid Truck communications.

**Thank you, your submission has been received!  
  
A member of our team will be in contact shortly.**

**Oops! Something went wrong while submitting the form.**

Fluid Truck

Explore

Top Cities

©2022 Fluid Truck, Inc. | [Terms](https://www.fluidtruck.com/terms-and-conditions) | [Privacy](https://www.fluidtruck.com/privacy-policy)
